in this lecture I will make another 3D
在这次演讲中，我将制作另一个3D
text effect using tiling to easily
使用平铺来轻松实现文本效果
create a pattern I click on the text
创建一个我在文本上点击的图案
tool and type 3D text I use shrikan
工具和输入3D文本我用的是虾虎
which is a free Google font I duplicate
这是我复制的免费Google字体
the text and drag it below I double
文本并将其拖到下面，我将其翻倍
click on it to get to the text tool I
单击它以转到文本工具I
press Ctrl a and type inkscape
按Ctrl a并键入Inkscape
click on the select tool I hold Ctrl and
按住Ctrl键并单击选择工具
drag the right side in to match the size
将右侧拖入以匹配大小
of the text above now I drag the text
在上面的文本中，现在我拖动文本
above to the right so that the T and the
右上角，这样T和
E show a straight line
E表示一条直线
I would like to have some curvature in
我想要有一些弧度。
the text to do this I have to convert
要做到这一点，我必须转换文本
the text to paths I select them both and
文本到路径我同时选择了它们和
go to path object to path
转到路径对象到路径
to curve 3D text I go to pathfx from the
要绘制3D文本曲线，我从
menu I choose envelope deformation I
菜单I选择封套变形I
click on the edit on canvas button at
点击在画布上编辑按钮
the right of bottom band path now I see
我现在看到底部频带路径的右侧
a green line at the bottom of the text I
正文底部的一条绿线是
can drag the line to curve the text at
可以拖动要在其上弯曲文本的线
the bottom
底部
now let's curve the text below I go to
现在让我们在下面的文本上画曲线，我转到
pathfx and choose envelope deformation I
Pathfx并选择封套变形I
select the edit on canvas button at the
选择位于的在画布上编辑按钮
right of top end path I control drag the
在我控制的顶端路径的右侧拖动
left note up and I drag the green line
左音符向上，我拖动绿色线条
down
降下来
I also control drag to write note up I
我还可以控制拖动来写纸条上的我
dragged the green line down again
再次拖拽绿线
I see I can drag the left note a bit
我明白了，我可以把左边的音符拖一点
further up and I can drag the green line
再往上走，我就可以拖着绿线
a bit further down
再往下一点
I want to compress the text a bit so I
我想把文本压缩一点，这样我
select them both
把它们都选上
I drag the text a bit in
我把文本往里拖了一点
to finalize the effect I go to path
要最终确定效果，请转到Path
object to path
对象到路径
now I will make them a single path
现在，我将使它们成为一条单一的路径
I want the 3d effect to go from light
我想让3D效果从光线中消失
blue to a darker blue I duplicate the
从蓝色到深蓝色我复制了
text and give it a darker blue I hold
文本，并给它一个深蓝色，我拿着
shift and control and make the duplicate
Shift和Control并复制
smaller I shift-click on the larger text
按住Shift键并单击较大的文本
I want to create a transition from One
我想要创建一个从
path to the other
通向另一个的路径
I go to extensions generate from path
我转到从路径生成的扩展
interpolate between paths I will make 50
在路径之间进行内插，我将生成50
copies in between them and click on live
在它们之间复制并点击LIVE
preview
预览
I click on apply and on close in my
我单击应用，然后在我的
layers I see a new group which are the
我看到了一个新的组，它们是
transitioning paths I will place the
过渡路径我将把
original light blue text on top and I
顶部的原始浅蓝色文本和我
will make it dark blue
会变成深蓝色的
I call the path top text I duplicate top
我将路径称为顶层文本，我复制顶层
text and call it pattern I go to fill
文本，并将其称为我要填写的样式
and stroke and for the fill I choose
和笔触，我选择了填充物
pattern
图案
for my pattern I choose abstract one now
对于我的模式，我现在选择抽象的模式
I will make my own pattern I click on
我会做我自己的模式，我点击
the ellipse tool I hold Ctrl and drag a
椭圆工具我按住Ctrl键并拖动一个
small circle I go to pathfx I choose
小圈子我选择去路径FX
tiling I will make 30 rows and 60
瓷砖I将排成30排和60排
columns
列
to get smaller circles at the top and
在顶部画更小的圆圈，
larger circles at the bottom I set scale
底部的圆圈较大，我设置了比例
to seven percent and I want to shift
降到7%，我想换个位置
each row 50 percent so I set offset to
每行50%，因此我将偏移量设置为
50. I zoom out and I will size the
50美元。我缩小并调整大小
pattern to fit the text I will make the
模式以适合文本，我将使
pattern White
花纹白色
to get the pattern covering the 3d
要获得覆盖3D的图案
effect I right click on the group and
Effect I右键单击组，然后
choose set clip group
选择设置剪贴组
I name the pattern circles I drag
我将我拖动的图案命名为圆
circles on the clip group I set the
剪辑组上的圆圈我设置了
opacity of circles to 25 percent with my
使用我的圆圈不透明度达到25%
arrow keys I now choose which part I
箭头键我现在选择哪个部分
like best of the circles I can also
喜欢最好的圈子，我也能
resize to get larger or smaller circles
调整大小以获得更大或更小的圆圈
I will create a black background I click
我将创建一个我点击的黑色背景
on the rectangle tool and drag over the
在矩形工具上，并将其拖到
canvas I press the space bar and click
画布我按空格键并单击
on Lower to bottom to make the edges
打开从下到下以生成边
visible I will add some Strokes
可见，我将添加一些笔划
I duplicate top text in my swatches I
我在样例中复制顶部文本
click on none and I shift click on White
单击None，然后按Shift键单击White
at the bottom right I scroll backwards
在右下角，我向后滚动
to set the stroke to half a millimeter
将行程设置为半毫米
I call the path white I duplicate the
我称这条小路为白色，我复制了
path twice I call the top layer blue and
路径两次我称顶层为蓝色
shift-click on the light blue Swatch I
按住Shift键并单击浅蓝色样本I
hide blue I click on white go to fill
隐藏蓝色我点击白色去填充
and stroke and stroke paint I set blur
和我设定的模糊笔触和笔触
to 10 percent I call the path white blur
到10%我称这条路为白色模糊
I shift click on white and choose group
我按住Shift键点击白色并选择组
I drag the group a bit down
我把这群人拖垮了一点
I reveal blue and scale it from the
我露出蓝色，并从
bottom
底部